Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- Air Line Agents Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Dispatcher - [Airline Safety and Economy in the Jet Age], 1961; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: Pamphlet for Air Line Dispatchers
- Air Line Agents Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Air Line Dispatcher, 1955; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.13:no.7 (1955)
  - Item 2: The Air Line Dispatcher, 1956; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.14:no.6-11 (1956)
  - Item 3: The Air Line Dispatcher, 1957; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.15:no.2 (1957)
  - Item 4: The Air Line Dispatcher, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.23:no.5 (1965)
  - Item 5: The Air Line Dispatcher, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.25:no.3 (1967)
  - Item 6: The Dispatcher - [Airline Safety and Economy in the Jet Age], 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Air Line Agents Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO backs drive to win voting rights for air line employees -, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: AIR, for Air Line Employees, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1:no.2-4 (1957-1958)
  - Item 3: Constitution and by-laws, 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Air Line Employees Assoc. Int'l., Our Story, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Handbook for Local Council Officers, Air Line Employees Assoc. Int'l., 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor's long hard road, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Air Line Agents Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of Air Traffic Control Committee, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: ALPA News, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.11 (1965)
  - Item 2: ALPA News, 1966; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-8,10-12 (1966)
  - Item 3: ALPA News, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1,3-8,11 (1967)
  - Item 4: ALPA News, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-2,7 (1968)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Arbitration award - between - Air Line Pilots Assoc, Int'l. Vs. Transcontinental & Western Air, Inc., 1946; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Interim report and Prelim. Recommendations - between American Airlines, Inc. and Air Line Pilots Assoc., 1954; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Air pilots dispute bring strike, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Air pilots unit backs strike vote, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Airline pilots elect new head, union says, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Arbiters Award $40-$100 Rises to TWA Pilots, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Behncke drops suit for air union post, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: court airs pilot dispute, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: David L. Behncke, 55, founded flier union, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Disputed pilot chief sees 'plot' on union, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Eastern air lines wins strike writ, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Halt engineer drive AFL tells its pilots, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: High-flying unionist, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Landis put forward to head pilots union, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Mohawk stalemate ends, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: NLRB takes case of air pilots aides, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Pan American Pilots get pay increases, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Pan American Pilots protest in London, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Pay row to ground line's new DC-6's, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Pilots hail Newark, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Pilots in lay-off seek other jobs, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Pilots seen defying courts, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Pilots' union head ruled in contempt, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Sayen grips pilot union controls, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Union funds' watch set, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: United signs pact pilots win rises, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Wildcat strike cuts EAL flights by 90%, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Striking noncombatants, 1952-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: NLRB orders union election, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Air Pilot upheld in Behncke ouster, 1951-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Air Pilot-Morale called very low, 1949-1952 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of Collision Avoidance Systems Standing Committee, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Author: Standing Committee on Collision Avoidance Systems
- Air Line Pilots Association, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Air Line Employee, 1972; Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Notes: 1972 September